It's unbelievable.
I never, ever, let my family
go without anything.
Sometimes I wasn't there because
I couldn't be, but even then,
I made sure everything was taken care of,
so I wasn't missed.
I never even cheated, guys.
Maybe in my mind, but, you know…
But the kids always had everything.
They ask for a lot.
"Dad, I want to take this class."
"I want a drone." "I want a tablet."
I give them what they want.
I keep going. For God's sake.
Then your phone rings.
"It's about a donation."
I don't know what I'm donating.
It's all automatic.
It's important that you understand
that if I'm not a good guy,
if I'm not a good father,
if I'm not a good husband,
then the concept of "good" is wrong.
Oh! Water!
So it's important that you all understand,
in my defense,
that what I'm going through is very hard.
WELCOME
DADDY'S IN TROUBLE
2 WEEKS EARLIER…
That's great. That is so great.
-Morning, pancake. How are you?
-Morning, honey.
Excuse me, sir, I'm sorry to bother you.
-Keep an eye on the sandwiches.
-Yep.
It's your kids' snack.
Super easy. Green light comes on, ready.
-Okay, honey.
-Okay?
Mom, you're so annoying!
You turn the AC off every day.
-It's so hot.
-Mom, where's my drone?
-I saw it near my closet.
-No. The drone flew away.
Nobody knows where it is.
It's breakfast time.
You're raising your daughter, right?
-Tom Tom is awake.
-Hi, sweetie. Good morning.
Good morning. No good morning for me?
-Morning, Mom.
-Great.
We don't have another thing.
Sandwiches. Daddy let them burn.
Honey, I'm busy.
I can't do everything at once,
for God's sake.
-Mom, we're out of granola.
-Hold on.
The cheese is watery from the fridge.
-Mom, the butter's too hard.
Hold on.
Since you're my lawyer and you're here,
can you help me with this contract?
I need to get this straight before work.
It's 146, 147, 148. And Clauses 3 and 1.
I'm not understanding the text.
I want to be sharp for work.
-Can you help me with this contract?
-What?
Come on, it's a huge company,
you can ask a lawyer to help you.
Yeah, Vicente could help,
but who needs Vicente
when I have the best lawyer
in town here at home?
-Former lawyer.
-Once a lawyer, always a lawyer.
-There are tricky parts. I think it--
-My dear, let me tell you something.
Every second I'm late,
the traffic gets worse.
If you took the kids to school,
you'd know, but that's not the case.
Let Mommy see, turn around. Look, it's…
-It will improve.
-Found it.
I can't help you right now!
I have to do her hair. God.
-Mommy will try again.
-I won't forget this, okay?
It will be prettier this time.
Let's go! We're late!
-Seriously, not now.
-But…
I can't believe it. Good morning, Simone!
-Mr. Fred is still here?
-He is. Listen.
I went to the market yesterday.
I bought chayote, zucchini…
Sweet potatoes were terrible.
Let's make broccoli rice today?
Let's go, guys!
-Let's go. That's it.
-Good morning!
-Let's go to school. You'll go with João.
-Oh, Tom Tom!
-Bye, Simone.
-I'll take the kids to school. Let's go.
Simone, excuse me. Did you get hurt?
You're limping. What happened?
No, it's just that one of my legs
is shorter than the other.
-Since when?
-Since I was born.
Do you know
what they have at school today?
The day of…
Fred, Simone has been with us
for seven years.
Just so you know.
You missed the limping for seven years.
See? I need your help.
I can't understand this contract.
-Hurry, give it to me.
-Thanks.
Let's go.
-Everyone have their seatbelts on?
-Yeah.
-Let's go.
Bye, Daddy. Bye.
-Kisses, Daddy.
-Bye.
Let's go.
WELCOME!
RABBIT HOME CENTER - ENTRANCE
MANAGEMENT
Hey.
Jerk.
Go away. I have nothing to say to you.
In Cambridge?
He speaks English, French,
all at the same time.
Jerk.
-Morning.
-Morning, Mr. Fred.
-Morning, Beth.
The coffee's terrible.
I messed it up today.
Great. You say "good morning,"
and take out the good.
Just drink it fast
because the Board's coming.
That's great.
…don't miss out on our exclusive deals.
These things make me so mad, you know?
We'll deal with it.
Matheus.
HUMAN RESOURCES
Of course my toilet can be art.
It depends on…
-Morning, Fred.
-Morning.
-Morning, Mr. Pontes.
Morning, Dante. Glad to see you here.
Everything okay?
Fred, Matheus has
something to show you. Please.
A cleaning staff employee was caught
on the security cameras.
What did she steal?
Wing screws. Three of them.
-Three boxes?
-No.
-Three screws.
-Oh, okay.
I thought…
We have a delicate situation on our hands.
Someone steals,
but they steal three items.
-Yeah.
-What do you do with this person?
What do you do?
Petty theft, nothing major, right?
You can't…
It's complicated. I think, to be fair,
we should issue a warning.
-Yes.
-We make an example of her.
For the company as a whole…
-No?
-Maybe.
What do you mean?
A warning? Today, it's three wing screws,
tomorrow it's an armed robbery.
-Robbery?
-Yes, that's true.
-Is it?
-It is.
It is. No, of course it is.
He's absolutely right.
And we have to lead by example.
We have to lead by example.
Here's what I propose.
A three-day suspension
so she can think about it.
-Sure.
-Right?
Three days. One for each screw.
I feel like you're downplaying
the offense, Fred.
-Maybe.
-Me?
-Yes.
-No…
I actually thought three days per screw.
You didn't let me finish
my train of thought.
Three days for each screw.
So, nine. Let's call it ten.
Yes. Makes sense.
In my opinion,
that lady should pay
for the entire stock of screws.
Hey.
Look.
I agree.
Guys, come on. Enough is enough!
Let's be rational here. 'Cause…
I'm noticing something very common.
Emotion's overtaking reason.
Enough, guys. I say we fire the lady now.
No, I agree. I agree.
We can't let reason be clouded by emotion.
-Exactly.
-Very good. Very good, Fred.
The termination paperwork's here.
Sign it, let's get this done.
I don't have my pen, because I…
Use mine.
Matheus.
-That was heavy.
-What the hell?
-That was unnecessary.
-At least it's two-for-one beers Tuesday.
-Nice.
-I want both.
I'll ask for one, get two,
and drink them, no sharing.
-What? Why so selfish?
-Selfish?
Look what I'm going through,
what Dante does to me.
-He's like a soap opera villain.
-No, Mr. Pontes is--
-He's more of a suck-up.
-So there are two villains.
-Two nuisances in my life.
-Yes.
Jesus. Good thing
it's two-for-one Tuesday,
because we really need and deserve it.
Yeah. You'll go home seeing double.
-To us.
-To our choices.
-And loved ones.
-To loved ones.
Yeah. Thanks, Marconi.
I appreciate it, buddy.
Being an adult sucks, man.
And we thought it would be easier. Right?
Roberta is the lucky one.
She's there smelling them…
You know? That's luck.
Clarice! I already told you to stop that.
Mom, João is breaking our TV deal.
I asked for five minutes, Mom.
Could you stop being so annoying?
-I'm hungry, Mom.
-Me too.
I'm only one person,
taking care of your brother.
-Where's Dad?
-He could bring pizza.
Oh, but today's Tuesday,
and Dad's partying.
He won't be home until ten.
-No.
-Give me the remote, João!
-Give me five minutes!
-Give it to me!
-I'm the oldest.
-You wouldn't give me five minutes.
Speaking of things we're thinking about…
His face is just like yours,
but it's better on him.
10:08 PM
Found it!
-Let's call the kids?
-Stop it, man.
Can I ask who let you stay up this late?
Even Tom Tom's awake.
He just fell asleep, and God help you
if you wake him up. Turn off the TV now.
João's playing the guitar
and you're not saying anything.
Because this scolding is for you.
João's scolding is being prepared
and will come his way soon.
Enough. Stop with the guitar.
God, Mom, can't you see I'm playing?
-I wanted to watch TV!
-I had the remote!
-I wanted!
-If I don't ask for--
Enough!
That's it!
No more zombies! No more guitar!
No more anything!
It's over, it's the Apocalypse!
I'll personally bring the Apocalypse
to this house! Enough!
What's going on, honey?
This isn't the Roberta I know.
Fred, you just witnessed a scene
which is hard to defend myself for.
Mommy's credibility
has taken a bit of a hit.
But if you had seen
the moments that led up to this,
you would understand.
But you didn't.
Because you weren't at home.
You were at the bar.
Living your best life with your bro.
So you didn't see it, right?
-Single mom.
-Honey, the kids.
Kids, go upstairs for a bit,
Mommy wants to talk
to Daddy about grown-up stuff.
Yes, go, Mommy wants to talk to Daddy.
-That was crazy.
-Just go.
Nicely done, huh, Roberta?
You wash your hands of it
and blame it all on the father?
You're the one washing your hands.
-Me?
-You weren't home, you went to the bar.
And vanished.
-Found it!
-Oh, Matheus, thank you.
-I'll throw it!
-Let me tell you.
Everything's wonderful, the barbecue…
But I need your help, everyone's help.
This barbecue needs to save my marriage.
Roberta hasn't looked me
in the eye since Tuesday.
So you got two-for-one beers
and two-for-one scoldings.
I wish it was only two-for-one.
I got five-for-one scoldings, one per kid,
plus one for Roberta.
So things are complicated, rough.
I had an idea. Maybe you could…
When we're eating,
you could talk me up a bit.
Praise me for making the barbecue…
Compliment me a little bit, all right?
-I'll improvise.
-Thanks.
If you forget, I'll give a signal.
-What?
-This is the signal.
-Be more discreet. That's it.
-Okay.
Who came up with the barbecue idea?
I'm so mad I'm about to become a vegan.
For us to meet up.
You needed to see your little sis.
"Little sister."
I loved the "little" part.
'Cause usually the little sister
is the younger sister.
Which is me, right?
Honey, I'm over 40, you're over 40.
None of us is young anymore.
But I just turned over 40, all right?
When I look back, I can see my 30s
right there. I can touch them.
-Hold it!
-Clarice! Stop with that ball now!
You don't see anything, Roberta.
Only diapers, pacifiers, school supplies.
Where's the Roberta
who wanted a tribal tattoo?
-Remember her?
-Geez.
-Do you remember?
-No. Please.
Thank God you didn't do it. Jesus Christ.
Honestly, it's a shame I didn't do it.
I should've done it, you know?
Like, a really bad tattoo.
A flower on my groin.
To have a mark on my body.
Telling a story
of a woman who just went for it.
That lived life. Who did crazy things.
-Love it.
-Oh my God!
-What?
-There's no flour for the farofa.
Shit, I almost died here, Roberta.
Bianca, honey. Come eat a chicken heart.
Daddy saved it.
Can I sleep at Fernanda's?
-Tonight?
-Yeah.
But, honey, it's Daddy's night.
-Please.
-You have a game.
No. You'll stay with Daddy.
You have to eat so you can
crush it in the game tomorrow.
-Yeah, Clacla, wait for Bianca.
-Honey?
Got you!
-Hey!
-Clarice, you're such a cheat, dude.
-I'm not.
-Yes, you are.
I'm not.
Who has the ball, you or us?
Thank God! Thank you, Lord!
Everyone's gonna stuff their faces
with farofa today. That's it.
Guaranteed constipation.
Isn't it? Mommy found it…
-What's that, Matheus?
-Stop!
-Now. Let's go.
-I'm starting to feel it!
-Let's go!
-Feeling it, Matheus.
-That's it!
Use the space. Watch Mr. Cruise over here.
-Give me the ball! Give it to me!
-No, I'm…
-Give it to me!
-No!
The meat is burning, man!
Fred! Fred, watch the girls!
They could explode, he wouldn't see it.
I'm going to go to Salvador
to do some interviews for my thesis.
-Really? Amazing!
-Yeah, and I'll spend a few days there.
Salvador is everything! You should come.
-Can you imagine?
I would love that.
Oh, there's juice on Mommy's leg.
How could I? Tell me, Renata.
Tell me how I could do that.
Tom Tom's adjusting to daycare this week.
Oh my God, there's so much juice.
-Give me the ball!
-No!
Give me the ball.
So much juice.
But Tom Tom has a father, right?
Work it!
Or does the Constitution say
the mom's responsible for daycare?
Clarice!
-I told Clarice to stop with the ball.
-Ouch, Mom!
Didn't I?
-I did.
-Mom, ouch!
No one listens. You know what I wanted?
Let them. Right? Just let them.
-Throw the ball. Go.
-Mom!
Mom, Dad's asking
if you're going to set the table.
What?
Guys, wait a second.
I heard Bianca is in the tennis
championship finals. Is that it?
We are, right?
Because I'm always right there with her.
If my daughter's dream is to be
a tennis player, it's my dream too.
Right?
Right.
He wants to say something.
Excuse me, I'd like to ask for a round
of applause to our barbecue chef!
-Me?
-Yeah.
Fred, I don't say so
as you're my best friend,
but it was very nice of you
to make this barbecue for our families.
-Thanks for letting me to be a part of it.
-Thanks for your words, my friend.
I didn't do anything at all.
I mean, obviously, everything I do
is for my wonderful family.
A round of applause!
And applause for the person
who bought the meat, made the salad,
set the table, takes care of the children.
No applause?
Of course.
A round of applause for Roberta.
Are you that ungrateful?
Let's give Mom a round of applause.
Come on!
More emphasis.
The older sister
won't applaud her little sister?
Seriously.
Wow, I always forget
that Aunt Renata is the oldest.
-Doesn't seem like it.
-Is she? Really? That's bizarre.
You want a chicken heart, honey?
Take a chicken heart.
It's delicious, honey.
Honey, there are little capybaras
doing water aerobics.
Geez, you have to see it.
Yay!
Go over there. To your side.
Honey, my side's your side,
and your side's my side.
Come on.
-You smell good.
-That's great, huh?
At least our scent doesn't age.
A person can be 109 years old,
but their perfume will still smell great.
-What are you talking about?
-I'm 42 years old.
But I look worn out. I look 109 years old.
But then again,
I take care of five children.
-How would I look?
-You're beautiful.
Wait, "five"? We have four children.
You're the fifth.
You can't do anything yourself.
-Me? Give me an example.
-Mm-hmm.
Honey, where's my towel?
Honey, didn't you buy butter?
Roberta, have you seen my salmon shirt?
It's like I have five children.
You think asking for help's bad?
It's a sign of humility.
To say, "I can't do this alone."
Honey, you have experience in the house.
You know the rhythm. I won't mess with it.
-You're joking?
-Betinha, you're overreacting, honey.
-Your life's just like any other mom's.
-Other moms are exhausted, overwhelmed.
Especially without a supportive husband.
I can't believe
you're saying I don't help.
Don't I feed Tom Tom when you ask me to?
Really, it's not about helping.
It's sharing the workload.
Doing what needs to be done
without me having to ask!
I won't argue. Know why?
You don't know what I go through.
You don't know what I go through at work.
Honestly, I think it's a privilege
you get the opportunity
to spend your days at home
with the most important thing
in life, our kids.
So, I said what I wanted.
That's it. I'd love to be in your shoes.
-Oh, really?
-Really.
Swear on your children's health?
Think carefully before you answer.
I swear.
Roberta, I can't believe
you're doing something so crazy.
Didn't you want to be in my shoes?
-This is your chance.
-It's bad timing.
I'm trying for a promotion.
-Dante won't get off my back.
-Ten days, Fred.
Really.
You wanted to be in my shoes so bad,
enjoying your family
and those beautiful children of yours.
-So here's your chance.
-You're only thinking about yourself.
Not about your children,
who are so nervous about this.
Tom Tom can't process mom's absence.
Guys, like I said,
Mommy's going on a trip.
Good for you, Mom. I wish I could go.
Yeah, Mom, go. Go have fun.
-Thank you, sweethearts.
-Mommy.
Dad!
She'll listen to you. She will.
Go on, honey.
Tell Mommy what you were
so nervously telling Daddy.
-What, honey?
-We're nervous about staying with Dad.
No!
Not about staying with Dad.
Staying with Dad's wonderful.
They're really nervous
to be without Mommy.
-Isn't that right?
-I messed up.
-You're afraid of the unknown?
-What "unknown," honey?
-It's my children, my house…
-Great. So come with me real quick.
It's all here.
Tuesdays, Thursdays, Clarice's jazz dance.
Malu has urban dance on Wednesdays.
João and Malu have swimming classes
on Mondays and Wednesdays.
Clacla has swimming classes
on Wednesdays and Fridays.
-Cool.
-And I'm adding you
to Clarice's swimming group,
João's swimming group,
and Malu's swimming group right now.
Don't worry. Jazz and urban dance
have only one group for the whole studio.
I'll add you to it too.
Oh, and I'll add you to the school group.
There's just one group
for all the parents.
-You'll love it. I'm adding you.
-Great.
Don't post stuff
on politics, soccer, or jokes.
They have enough to talk about all day.
No need to innovate.
What is this? Roberta?
NEW CHLORINE BRAND?
THAT GIRL WHO BITES OTHER KIDS
FERNANDA GOT OUT OF JAZZ 10 MINUTES EARLY
Roberta?
Guys, ten days will fly by.
And Salvador is so close.
Everything will be fine.
Listen to your dad.
-I love you.
-Honey…
Mommy loves you. Bye. Be good, okay?
-Have fun, Mom.
-Don't forget to bring us presents.
Go nuts, Mom.
Don't go nuts, okay, honey?
Come back in one piece, God.
Bye.
-Bye.
-Bye. Mommy loves you.
Mommy…
-Let's play. I'll start.
-I'm in.
Dear Lord.
Just a second.
For the love of God, man.
I abandoned my children, Renata.
-Oh my God, ten days. I'm a monster.
-No, you're not.
I only think of myself. I'm so tired.
I only think about how tired I am,
and that's selfish.
They're kids. Go back, sir.
-Don't go back.
-I won't.
-My chest hurts.
-Calm down.
-I don't wanna go.
-It's fine.
It's only ten days, relax.
They're happy for you.
Did you hear this baby crying?
Is it Tom Tom?
-It's Tom Tom.
-Roberta…
He must be thinking,
"Why'd Mommy leave me?"
We're in the car, going to the airport.
There's no baby here. Right, sir?
-No baby.
-It's a sign.
It's Tom Tom.
Mothers have superhuman hearing.
You wouldn't know, you haven't lived it.
-It's not Tom Tom.
-I have a little one.
It's not Tom Tom. And even if it is,
he has a father and three siblings.
-He even has Simone.
-He has Simone.
-No one's going to die.
-He has Simone. Thanks.
-No one will die.
-We'll have fun, right?
-It'll be great!
-It will be good, right?
-Yes, it'll be good, great.
-We'll have a piña colada!
What have I done?!
How could I ever live
Without your, without your
Without your company?
Son, I've sung this 86 times.
How about in English?
Nobody can stand two hours
47 minutes to put a kid to bed,
adding two plus seven is nine…
that's a lot of time.
Honey, it's late.
Turn that off and let's go to bed.
Dad, are you sure we'll survive
without Mom?
Yes.
Let's go to bed.
My sweethearts.
Beautiful kids, good morning.
-It's not!
-We missed first period.
How irresponsible of you!
-Why didn't you get up?
-No one turned the AC off.
Let's go, guys. Let's go.
Everything's under control.
You'll have a delicious breakfast
made by Daddy, who loves you very much.
We're about to miss second period.
Hey, leave it. Shut up.
Sweethearts, if you thought
you'd miss Mommy's delicious food,
look what you're getting.
-No. What is this?
-Daddy's delicious food.
Look at all these options.
This is good, guys.
So delicious! How is it, honey?
What kind of cheese is this?
-No. Too much fried food.
-You always ask to go to the US.
Fried food?
That's all they eat in the US, honey.
You can't complain.
It's hard to do things in a rush,
but this is delicious.
Everyone needs to eat well
to get to school strong, healthy,
to learn a lot of wonderful things.
-Eat some grapes.
-Dad, put some butter on my bread.
Don't you have a mom, honey?
I mean, don't you have hands?
This has nothing to do with mothers.
I meant hands!
Spread the butter
with your own hands, okay?
Wow, Dad, this breakfast is delicious.
You really surprised me.
The thing is, there's only enough for me.
-We need more.
-Next time, you help me.
-Come on.
-You can have mine.
I don't want this, it's disgusting.
Malu, I won't let you say
the food's disgusting.
You do all kinds of disgusting things.
Who wants delicious eggs made by Daddy?
-Damn it, Clarice, come on!
-No, wait. Malu, no.
-Stop!
-Girls, stop it right now.
-Don't burp.
-Ew!
-Good one, João! Burp!
-Do not burp.
-Burp!
Do not-- Do not burp!
Are you trying to drive me crazy?
It's only breakfast. Everyone's going
to school on an empty stomach!
With your clothes all dirty!
I don't even care.
Don't like what I said and did?
I don't care, because I've had enough!
I've had enough!
-Mr. Fred?
-Simone!
Is everything okay?
Everything's great.
My credibility as a father
has taken a bit of a hit.
But you didn't see the moments
that led up to this.
It's only the first day.
-Let's go, Dad!
-Let's go, Dad, we're late.
Okay! Calm down.
This kid won't stop pooping!
I don't understand anything he says.
Simone, how are you?
I know you work three times a week,
but could you come for ten straight days?
It's for the kids, mostly.
-All right, Mr. Fred.
-Thank you so much.
-Let's go.
-Yes.
-Yes!
-Come here, son.
-Here's Tom Tom's mango.
-Mango!
Thank you.
-I don't understand you.
-Bye, my dear.
-I missed two classes.
-You didn't miss anything.
You got to spend time
with your family, your siblings.
Eating mango, everyone's happy.
What was the class?
-Geography.
-Geography?
Geography is mango, it's land, it's miome.
Biome!
See? I don't even remember.
If you're not gonna be a geographer,
you don't need…
Thanks. You don't need Geography.
Son, wet wipes, please.
I had two Portuguese classes,
which I missed.
We're speaking Portuguese now.
You didn't miss it. Do you understand me?
We're communicating
perfectly in Portuguese,
so you know Portuguese.
Wet wipes. He's all dirty.
-What class did Clacla have?
-English.
English? But-- Wet wipes.
No one learns English in school.
You didn't enroll us in an English course
because you said
we were already learning at school.
-Did I say that?
-Yes.
No, that's for later.
We'll learn English at another time.
I don't understand you, okay?
I don't understand you, honey.
-Wet wipes, João!
-I'm looking, Dad, they're not here!
-How?
-You didn't put them here.
-If you had, they would be here.
-No wipes. Let's go?
-Let's go!
-Let's go. Finally.
Help me with him.
Oh, sweethearts.
-Have a nice day.
-Dad, why did you stop here?
What do you mean? It's your school.
We don't go here anymore,
we switched schools last year.
The frog won't wash his feet
He won't wash them
Because he doesn't want to
He lives down by the little pond
He won't wash his feet
Because he doesn't want to
What a stinky smell!
Little butterfly's in the kitchen
Making chocolates for her godmother
Poti, poti
Wooden leg
Glass eye
And a woodpecker's beak, beak, beak…
Now, really fast.
Just a second.
It's the same song, but faster.
Making chocolates for her godmother
Poti, poti
Wooden leg…
It's the same song.
My love told me…
Son, say goodbye to Dad.
That the flower of the field is rosemary…
-Very good!
-He's settled in.
He's great, right, son?
Can you stay a little longer?
Rosemary, golden rosemary
That grew in the field
Without ever being sown
It was completely unexpected, guys.
And since I had
a few vacation days I needed to take,
it all worked out,
because she really had to go.
And it's only ten days, right?
Ten days fly by.
But it's the opening week
for the new branch.
-True.
-Not a good time.
It's family, guys.
We do anything for family.
Speaking of family, Pontes,
how is that wonderful wife of yours, uh…
-Ivone.
-Ivone, wonderful Ivone.
I asked Roberta to bring back some gifts.
No, there's no need.
Stop it, Pontes, don't be like that.
Who doesn't love
those little cocadas from Bahia?
I asked her to bring 10, 15, 20 of them.
-Who doesn't love them?
-A diabetic?
I really wanted to thank you
for the doctor you recommended.
My wife is very happy with him.
No worries, Mr. Pontes, I'm happy to help.
Speaking of gifts,
my wife is going to New York.
She can bring back some perfume,
a purse, a real gift.
-No, there's no need.
-Yes.
And don't worry,
this trip was already planned,
I won't miss any work.
There's no need. Nonsense.
SWIMMING CLASS 1
SWIMMING CLASS 2
What's the need to connect human beings?
STUDENTS' PARENTS GROUP
DANCE CLASSES - PARENTS
Humans hate each other.
I'll mute everything.
Quiet, turn it off.
God, my thigh.
You should've done it, okay?
-No way.
-You'll regret it.
Everyone's looking.
Yeah, because you're such a tourist.
-No, it's pretty. Everyone loves it.
-I just met her.
-Everyone's looking.
-You're not like me. I'm a local.
People think I'm a local.
-Wow, she's a-- Sure, she's a local.
-What are you doing?
Calling Fred?
No.
Calling my informant.
Hi, Ms. Roberta.
Simone! Simone, my love, I miss you.
How was the first day? Tell me.
Terrible.
Great!
What happened? I want details.
Who did what? What happened?
Mr. Fred ran me over.
I know, honey. He does that.
He doesn't give us a chance.
-He just gets in our way. I know that.
-No, Ms. Roberta.
You don't understand.
He ran me over with his car.
He hit me with his car.
-My God.
-I went to the hospital.
Simone, are you okay?
Well, I'm here, resting.
I won't be able to go on for a week.
I just can't.
-Of course.
-But look, if you want,
I can send my niece to help Mr. Fred.
And if I were you, I would want that,
because things are not good over there.
Really? Things are not good.
My niece is excellent.
"Excellent" is a bit much, Simone.
Yeah. That's not what I'm looking for.
She'd do everything
while Fred sits back and relaxes?
No, thank you.
To be honest,
there's nothing excellent about her.
She's never worked in a family home,
can't keep a job,
she came here to try her luck
and now here she is, living off me.
That's what I call excellent.
Love it. Great résumé.
Go ahead and send her to my house.
I'm really glad I found a job for her.
And she can give Mr. Fred
a little help, right?
A little. I mean a little.
I don't want her doing everything for him.
Don't worry. It's a deal.
-Bye, get well soon.
-Okay, bye.
Look…
She's gone.
-Fred ran over Simone.
-Huh?
Come on!
Good job, honey.
-What do you want?
-I don't get what he's saying.
Red, right? Red.
Guys, please, give me a break.
Please, take a breath, stop running.
Guys, please.
You keep leaving
your clothes all over the house.
-Dad.
-Yes, honey.
Where's my birth certificate?
Oh my God. Is that a challenge?
How am I supposed to know that?
Well, you're my father.
Why don't you know?
Dads need to know everything?
Why do you need it?
I want to know what time I was born
to make my birth chart.
-You were born at 9 p.m.
-You're making that up.
-No one is born on the dot like that.
-You were, honey.
The doctor was great.
Had a big beard. He said,
"Congratulations,
your daughter is extremely punctual."
And you still are. That's it.
I can't believe it, Dad.
You're making fun of me.
Absolutely.
And please stop leaving all this stuff
around the house.
-That's not mine.
-It's not? Huh.
Malu…
Weird.
João. Look at all these clothes.
-Give me that.
-Huh?
What is this?
-I was studying with a friend.
-What friend?
Clacla! What are you holding,
for God's sake?
What is this? What is this, kids?
Go away, cockroach!
What is this? These children are insane!
What is this, guys?
Pedro, wait! This is bug spray, guys.
My eye! Jesus.
-What is it?
-Who just walked by?
-No one.
-What?
-You shouldn't even be here.
I'm the owner of the house
with roach spray in my face.
Shouldn't I be in my own house, man?
Look. Urban dances for Malu,
pick up Clacla from swimming with Enzo.
So neither you nor they
should be here now.
I picked up Clacla and Enzo.
And Malu's dance class?
No. Clacla?
No. Clacla, Enzo…
Stop it. You're going to get that
all over the house.
-My name's Natan.
-Yes, his name's Natan.
Where's Enzo?
Enzo! Oh my God.
Oh my God. I'm sorry.
Uncle Fred. Nice to meet you.
I'm not your uncle.
Kids call grown-ups "uncles,"
but I'm not your uncle, or family.
Just to be clear. You look great.
Listen, this is very important.
Forget all that trauma stuff.
Parents are the ones who traumatize kids.
"But he abandoned me." No! I didn't.
To be an abandonment,
it has to come
from an actual parent, okay?
God.
Jesus.
My love.
I miss you.
Oh my God.
Wait. Just a second, hey!
For the love-- Hello?
Wait a minute, you crazy beast!
Go away!
What is this?
-Hey, son.
-That's embarrassing.
Using Clacla's goggles?
-Shouldn't you sleep for class tomorrow?
-No. We don't go to school tomorrow, Dad.
But why?
Sweetie, it's important.
I thought whoever didn't go
could stay at school.
Isn't it wrong to leave
a bunch of kids at home all day?
Give them a multiplication table.
Make them draw, or something.
-Mr. Fred, right?
-Fred.
Mr. Fred, listen, almost 100%
of the students went on the field trip.
You decided not to go.
-Why didn't you want to go?
-You wouldn't let us.
-I wouldn't?
-Yes.
-But why?
-It's too expensive.
Expensive? No.
Can I pay with Pix? I can pay right now.
Now it's too late, Mr. Fred.
For the love of God, take these kids.
They're wonderful, they're tame.
Give him a melon, he'll be happy.
They don't even need to study.
They can chase a rabbit or something!
Let's do an-- Let's play at school?
-Mr. Fred.
-He wants to play at school.
Unfortunately,
there's nothing I can do to help you.
Guys, here's the deal.
Dad had a wonderful idea.
Let's take a beautiful family picture.
So society can see
what a modern and woke father I am,
spending time with my family,
taking care of you, the house,
and that I love you.
You're a modern father now?
Let's take a picture, come on.
Come on, Malu.
Please, honey. It'll be beautiful.
Look at all these beautiful people.
Look, Tom Tom. Everybody smile.
One, two, three…
I'll post it right away. Wait.
Malu, you look so grumpy.
-I'll put an emoji over your face.
-Do what you want!
What…
Mommy's calling. Let's talk to Mommy.
Everyone sit down, Mommy's calling.
Oh my God. Let's answer Mommy.
Everybody.
-Hi, Mommy!
-Hi, honey! Hi, everyone!
Tom Tom! Oh, Mommy loves you.
Mommy loves you. Hi, Joãozinho, Clacla.
Where's Malu?
Honey, Malu is in such a bad mood.
Psychology should study her bad mood.
But everything's okay, wonderful.
And the house?
How is it? Is it still standing?
It's wonderful. Right, guys?
-Of course.
-Yeah.
Hey, Roberta.
Why's the camera so close to your face?
We can't see Bahia.
Where's Bahia? This is weird.
-We want to see Bahia.
-Honey, I have a surprise.
What do you mean, surprise?
-No!
-No, we don't want any surprises.
-What is it?
-Mommy did something crazy.
What did you do? Tom Tom's here.
I got a hair wrap!
What do you mean?
Guys, Daddy needs to have
a private conversation with Mommy.
We'll talk later. Everything's fine.
What, Roberta?
What wrap are you talking about?
Isn't it great? And do you know
what else I got?
A tattoo.
A tribal tattoo in a place
I can't reach to show you now.
But I'll show you later, you'll love it.
A tribal tattoo?
What else are you doing down there?
Is there something going on?
You're acting weird.
What's up, Fred?
-It's henna, it comes off.
-When? When you come back?
What else are you doing
I don't know about?
Listen, those kids
don't even give me time to breathe,
I couldn't even cheat on you
in my thoughts.
-What is going on?
-So? Let's go to Praia do Forte?
-Let's go to Praia do Forte!
-Are you on the phone?
-Yeah.
-Hi, Fred!
Rê is saying hi.
I have to go. My battery's about to die,
so I might be hard to reach.
Hard to reach? Honey, listen.
There are faithful women,
unfaithful women,
and women with no battery on their phones,
headed to Praia do Forte,
with a lot of hair wraps
around their body, and a new tattoo.
Oh my God.
With self-esteem through the roof.
I'm glad you think that way.
Bye, honey, I love you.
Send kisses to the kids.
-Oh, look! It's Gerson, the henna guy.
-Who's Gerson?
-It's my husband. Bye, honey!
Bye, Fred!
My God!
Oh, no. No, man.
MATHEUS
CALLING…
Hello. Hi, Matheus.
Ready for a bombshell?
What do you mean?
Pontes is retiring.
Wait. Who's taking his place?
That could be my chance, right?
More like Dante's.
But why Dante's?
I've been with the company longer.
-Dad, can you play with me?
-Not now, honey. Take Daddy's computer.
I'll let you use it today.
Oh my God, this can't be.
Dad, having yesterday's pizza
for today's breakfast
wasn't good, I feel really sick.
Can't you see
I'm on a very important work call?
-Help me clean up this mess.
-What's "Xvideos"?
Just a second, Matheus.
Hold on, sweetie, this is…
Xvideos…
Dad, I can't reach Mom.
I need to talk to her, it's serious.
-You can tell me anything, honey.
-No, it has to be Mom!
-Damn it!
-Damn it.
-Matheus, I'll call you in a minute.
-Okay.
Honey?
Can I come in?
Talk to Daddy.
-It's a woman thing.
-A woman thing?
My underwear got stained.
Did you poop your pants, honey?
It's the pizza.
Your brother's got the same thing.
Completely normal.
Let me tell you. Back in college,
Dad once mixed booze
with some greasy street food.
I pooped my pants.
Took the whole semester off.
Dad!
I got my period.
But here, in this…
In this pink room, with all these…
All these dolls and little monsters?
That doesn't make sense, honey.
These dolls are Clarice's.
Damn.
That's beautiful, honey.
It's all right.
Okay?
That's beautiful.
It's all right, honey.
It's all right, okay?
You're beautiful. That's just nature.
Everything's fine, okay? It's connected.
Now you're more…
You've always been,
you're nature before birth.
So, nature has its own--
Listen, when a bee dies,
the whole balance of nature
gets thrown off.
It's all interconnected.
The cycle of the moon, the ocean.
-Women are the moon too.
-Okay, Dad.
But what do I do about the blood?
Just a second.
Wait. You know Daddy gets--
I can't handle blood. Hang on.
Get Dad a glass of water,
I'm dizzy, for the love of God.
Honey!
-Dad!
-Hold on a second, honey.
I'll look it up.
First period. What to do?
Mom's away, dad's fucked. Search.
Sorry, I didn't get that.
-Dad's fucked.
-Dad, take me to my swimming lesson.
One second, for God's sake.
Nothing's coming up.
-Dad, I don't feel good.
-How come?
-Dad.
-Hold on, honey.
Oh, no.
Hang on a second.
No.
Screw it.
Screw Pontes! Screw Dante!
Screw it all!
Guys…
Daddy needs five minutes alone, okay?
Dad, have you given up on us?
No, I haven't given up on anyone.
I just need to be alone a minute.
Are you smoking again?
If you put that cigarette in your mouth,
I'll never speak to you again.
-Really, honey?
-Really!
Dude, you're such a child.
Yes, I am. I am immature.
-Hey. No.
-Can I tell you something?
-Being an adult sucks.
-Okay? No.
"It gets better when you're older, when…"
No, it doesn't get better. It sucks.
Especially with one, two, three, four.
Four people calling me "Dad" all the time.
Two of them are teenagers now.
Full of demands.
Everyone wants everything.
I can't believe life on Earth
has decided this is normal.
Honey, you used to be
a sperm cell, sweetie.
You came from me,
went to your mother's egg,
and boom, now you have your own eggs.
I just can't believe this is normal.
Are you following Daddy? Life's crazy.
Okay, but you can't smoke.
Honey, listen, I'm not asking
for your permission. This is mine.
-I can have this one minute. This is me.
-You're not smoking.
Honey, that's my right.
Dad needs to push back against life.
Guys, the door slammed shut
and Tom Tom's inside.
-Are you serious?
-Yes.
My God!
There's not a single adult around here!
-Tom Tom!
-Jesus!
-Can you hear me? Open up!
-Dad!
Let me help you, hold on.
Another window. Another window!
-What is going on?
-He's just sitting down.
No, Tom Tom. No.
-Let's call a locksmith.
-Does anyone have their phone?
-No.
-Mine's inside.
Dad, do something.
-What now?
-Oh, no.
Guys, I need to get to Tom Tom
before he reaches that outlet, okay?
-It's fine.
-What are you doing?
-What do you mean?
-Trust me.
-Everything will be fine.
-No, Dad!
Guys, everything will be fine.
It's Daddy, okay?
-Oh my God.
-This is not going to work.
-It's fine.
-Be careful, Dad.
Everything will be fine.
-Dad!
-Dad, hold on tighter.
-Just a second.
-Dad, hold on.
Jesus…
Put your foot down first.
-There.
-Daddy's here.
It's gonna work, guys.
It's going to work, okay?
I got this far already.
I got this far, this is already…
It's already…
-Guys, is that Mr. Fred?
-Yes.
-Yes. We don't have the key.
-I have the key.
Mr. Fred! The key!
I have the key, Mr. Fred!
-Where?
-Here!
My God!
-He's screwed.
-What do we do?
He passed out.
You scared me, dude.
-Where are my kids, Matheus?
-Relax, they're at home.
They're with the new girl
that's replacing Simone.
She's such a character.
But everything's okay, relax. Calm down.
Here. Look, guys, it's like that.
Oh, that's so pretty.
The "Clean me up, Mommy" position.
Put your legs up just like Tom Tom.
Got it?
That's the figure-eight move, guys.
But I want you to do the figure-four move,
the one we practiced earlier.
-Okay?
-Okay.
Front, side, back, side.
Is it hard? Yes.
Because that's a funk classic.
Even your dad knows this one.
Now, faster. Front, side, back, side.
You're laughing, huh?
You think it's funny?
I'll teach you something.
I'll teach you how to approach a girl
to make her weak in the knees,
but not to qualify as harassment.
-Got it?
-Got it. Go on.
Calm down, in my own time, man.
Relax, big guy.
Let's go.
Hey. How are you doing?
That's it. You say that, and that's it.
That's it. Can he touch her?
-No.
-No. If you touch her, you're out.
You're out.
It's over. Forget it.
Now that one's going to be trouble.
Look at his little face.
Little rascal.
Come here, you little rascal.
Come here, honey.
Come here. God, he threw everything.
You're going to be trouble,
because you're a little rascal.
-Dad?
-Oh! Hi, guys.
-Daddy!
-God, I missed you, my loves.
Careful with Daddy's arm, it hurts.
-How are you?
-Oh, Dad.
This is Brenda, Simone's niece.
-She can come every day, okay?
-Yeah, Dad, she's really cool.
Dad, seriously, she's really cool.
-Thank you.
-And what were you doing just now?
-Just so I know.
-Now?
-Yeah.
-We were… We were studying math.
-Yeah!
-Square root of eight.
-Right?
-Yes.
A new Pythagoras thing.
And João asked me to help him
with the obscene triangle.
No, I mean, the Bermuda Triangle.
-Did you ask that?
-I did.
-Right?
-Playground.
-Playground?
-What did he say?
Do you want to go
to the playground? Playground!
Bye, people!
We're going to the playground.
-Bye, guys!
-Bye!
Playground!
See? She understands what he says.
-Mr. Fred. Excuse me.
-Hey, Brenda.
I'm sorry if I did anything wrong.
I joke around like that for fun.
The kids like it.
It keeps them entertained.
Don't worry, it was great.
Let me ask you something.
What kind of work did you do before?
Just so I know.
-Me?
-Yes.
I worked at a garment factory,
on the administrative side.
I worked with numbers and all that.
And I left
because something better came up.
At a friend's cake factory.
She wanted me there
because of my experience.
I went to work with her, it worked out,
but now I'm taking it easy
because I want to go back to college.
I'll be honest with you.
My dream, my real dream in life,
is to own my own publishing house.
-Oh, that's so cool.
-Yeah.
-I want to be a translator.
-That's great. Really great.
-It's nice, right?
-Very cool.
So, that's it, Mr. Fred.
I think I should go,
or I'll get stuck in traffic.
-Yes. I'll walk you out.
-So I better go.
-Thank you.
-Before you leave,
can you give me the number
for your friend's cake factory?
Because I had an idea.
I can pick up some cake for the kids.
They'll love it.
-The friend I said I worked for?
-Yeah.
It's closed, Mr. Fred.
The pandemic, you know?
-It's closed.
-I see.
-What a shame.
-Okay. See you soon.
Thank you for everything. It was great.
-Mr. Fred.
-Yes.
-I'm sorry, Mr. Fred.
-Sorry?
I didn't mean to lie to you, but I did.
-What?
-I lied, Mr. Fred.
What I just told you was actually
more of an idealized version of things.
It's what I dreamed of being in life.
What I really am is someone
who bounces from job to job.
-That's okay.
-The last one was last week.
They fired me
because of three wing screws.
Can you believe it?
-Three wing screws?
-Yes.
-Where?
-Rabbit Home Center, do you know it?
-No.
-Mr. Fred, that place is horrible.
Honestly, I can't stand rabbits anymore.
-The animal rabbit!
-Yes.
I'm triggered.
I don't know how Easter is gonna be.
If I see a rabbit, Mr. Fred,
I might punch it.
-The rabbit and the man that fired me.
-Wait a second. It's okay, come here.
Follow me. Take a seat, please.
Do you, by any chance,
know the guy that fired you?
Of course not, Mr. Fred.
If I knew the man who fired me,
he wouldn't be alive anymore!
-Calm down.
-He wouldn't.
I would grab him, sit him down,
grab a pair of tweezers,
and pull out every hair on his body,
nice and slow.
Why did you steal? You stole!
I was going to buy it,
but when I got to work,
can you believe a box
with 100 wings screws fell on my head?
I was honest.
I should have stolen all 100.
I only stole three,
there were 97 left in the box.
-Was that fair?
-No.
For them to fire me like that,
kick me to the curb?
-Never.
-They fired me and gave me nothing.
That place is bad.
They treat the employees so poorly.
-You have no idea.
-Yes.
They screw us so much.
If we don't screw them a little,
we'll go crazy.
But did you do that before? Steal?
Of course not, Mr. Fred. No way.
For God's sake, I was just launching
this personality trait.
-Oh, okay.
-Where do you work?
-You're a lawyer, right?
-Me?
Yeah, you're a lawyer.
I am.
I knew you were, because I saw
so many law books upstairs.
-In the office.
-That's right.
-Mr. Fred, I have to go, okay?
-Hm-hmm.
-But I'll be back tomorrow.
-Sure.
-Okay?
-I'll be waiting.
-If you need anything…
-Sure.
Article 93, huh?
Honey, Tom Tom just fell asleep.
Come here.
About that thing,
Daddy researched everything.
I already talked to Brenda.
She told me everything.
Brenda? I'm glad you brought her up.
Don't you think Brenda
seems a little strange?
Because Dad can think
of other options, okay?
Dad, if you fire Brenda,
I'll learn how to drive
and run you over, okay?
-Jesus, honey, Dad just thought--
-No, Dad.
Give Daddy a kiss…
Thank you, son.
Mr. Fred!
The girls' snacks, you almost forgot.
Thank you so much. You're wonderful.
-Thank you.
-No worries.
Have a good day at school.
Here, girls, your snacks. Thank you.
You're lovely.
Geez.
WELCOME!
RABBIT HOME CENTER
ENTRY
-Mr. Fred!
-Jesus, what the heck?
-Beth?
-Come here!
You look like you're on stakeout.
-Come.
-Couldn't you wait?
I'm desperate, Mr. Fred.
You know that Family Day,
the company's celebration,
is the day after tomorrow, right?
I know, Beth, but look,
Roberta is not home,
my kids won't want to come,
I won't force them,
and I don't know if you heard,
but I fell off the balcony.
Okay, Mr. Fred,
but the whole Board is going.
Mr. Dante and his entire family
will be there.
You know those margarine commercials
with a mom who looks like a model
and two beautiful kids
whose bright smiles are so white
it could blind you?
That's Mr. Dante's family.
They look like TV stars.
Look what he did to get everyone excited.
You better bring your kids.
I was going to send it to you,
but I thought it was better if you came.
To see it in person. Who knows,
maybe you'll bump into Mr. Pontes.
The more you're seen,
the harder you are to forget.
Beth, for the love of God,
I've only been gone a few days.
Nobody's forgotten me yet.
You think?
It's just that some people
only have to be gone for a little while
to be forgotten.
You better bring your children.
So, you're here
because she's there with Tom Tom.
Exactly.
And you were the one
who fired her from here?
Exactly.
And she doesn't know who you are?
Exactly. In other words,
I'm sleeping with the enemy.
No, she is.
She's the one who lost her job,
she's the one who got fired,
you're the villain.
-Come on, man.
-What?
Pontes.
-Wait a second.
-Straighten up, man.
Here.
Pontes.
I missed you. I mean, that's not it.
Thank you for the vacation, because…
Family Day is coming up, huh?
What a wonderful energy.
How's everything?
The planning,
your wonderful wife, how is she?
She's not well.
She had a stroke.
Pontes…
Man, what the hell?
Sorry, Pontes is taking time off
because of his wife's health.
How could you forget to tell me
the most important thing on the planet?
-My bad, I messed up.
-No, you really did.
-I know I messed up.
-But you really messed up.
Fine. I tried to tell you, I tried.
Guys, look. Dad has many flaws, all right?
Dad has many flaws, makes mistakes,
but we're here to improve.
So, what did we do?
I asked you to write down one thing
that would improve our lives.
Where is it?
-I know mine, Dad.
-Really?
-Yes.
-Everyone know their wishes?
-We will throw our paper into the fire,
the fire will go up,
and our lives will get…
-Better!
-So let's throw them in. One, two, three.
Come on, Tom Tom, you too.
Get better, wonderful life!
Throw it to the universe!
Yes!
Guys, I don't want to intrude.
But what did you ask?
I asked for love, the end of patriarchy,
harmony among all people, and world peace.
That's my wonderful daughter.
I'm proud of you, honey.
I love you.
-What about you, son?
-I asked to be rich.
A practical person.
A person who knows what he wants.
I'm very proud of you, son.
What about you, Clacla?
I asked for unity in our family.
Oh my-- This is for you.
This is for you. You are wonderful!
Daddy will tell you what I asked for.
I asked for us to do more things together.
"But we already do
a lot of things together."
But a truly united family,
like our ancestors, is always together.
I asked for us to party together,
go to the movies,
restaurants, play video games, play ball.
Maybe to go to Family Day together.
Look at that.
-Oh no! God forbid.
-No way, I'm not going.
Guys, Family Day is very important.
All our ancestors have done it.
We sing to the fire, the forest,
the woods, the moon, the sun.
Let's do that, guys.
Let's use our teas,
our weed!
-No, not weed. Did I say "weed"?
-Yes.
-No, not weed.
-I heard it.
No, honey. I talk to you all day
and you don't ever listen to me.
When you're not supposed to list--
-Bye!
-Bye? Honey, no.
-Excuse me.
-No weed! Keep the fire in your heart.
Yes, honey, help me out. Look.
The important thing's
that everyone goes to Family Day.
Hey, hey, hey
To Family Day
Hey, hey
Convince my siblings
To Family Day
Yes!
-To Family Day!
-Let's go to Family Day!
Let's go! Fire!
Heading to the fire of love!
If you don't want to think about Dad,
who does everything for you,
think about yourselves.
This company pays for our life.
You need to go to Family Day.
Okay. If you can say
three things that I like,
I'll go.
Honey, that's easy.
You like ice cream, pizza,
and boys.
Are you a lesbian, honey?
Daddy will love you just the same.
-This is amazing.
-Ugh, Dad!
Three things I like.
Me specifically.
Come on, honey.
Grapes, honey. Grapes!
Son, didn't you ask to be rich?
The thing at the fire blew up.
Feels like a bad omen.
If I lose this job,
boom, we're poor immediately.
But if we crush it on Family Day,
that's success, a promotion, money.
We'll get closer to what you asked for,
my wonderful son.
Great, Dad.
But if I go,
I want to throw a party here at home.
-Who?
-Me.
-Are you blackmailing me?
-Oh my God.
Are you becoming a bad person?
So, I'm not going.
You're a bad person!
My son became a bad person.
Cecília, thank you. Everything you said
is super useful for my research.
This is going to be wonderful.
I don't even know how to thank you.
-You're wonderful.
-Thank you.
-I'll email you.
-Okay.
-I'll be waiting. Thanks.
What is it, Beta?
I'm so happy to be here with you.
To watch you working.
Work is so important, right?
It's so good to do what we love, right?
-Yes!
-Wow, that was very cool.
I was nervous. Did you see?
No. You were nervous?
You looked so confident.
-Yeah?
-You were articulate. Wonderful.
I'm so glad you were here, sis.
-It was beautiful.
-Thank you.
-I'm still cold.
-Come on, take a sip.
-For the love of God.
-Go.
-Can you order another one?
-Yes. Excuse me?
Two more.
I'll go to Family Day.
You can thank Brenda.
Brenda?
Why do I have to sweep--
-Brenda?
-Yes.
How did you pull off the miracle
of getting her to go to Family Day?
Look, Mr. Fred,
I'm not trying to be annoying.
But we have those words in Portuguese.
Dia da Família.
-Yeah. But what did you do?
-Just so you know.
-It was simple.
-What do you mean, simple?
Nothing about that is simple.
To say it's simple is humiliating.
What did you do?
I just had to tell her
that it was important to you.
Yeah.
Are you serious? Brenda, thank you.
-No problem.
-I don't even know how to thank you.
-Thank you so much.
-That's it.
Mr. Fred, come here.
Let me tell you something quick.
-Yes.
-Since you're here.
You said you don't know how to thank me.
-Right?
-Right.
Yeah, but I know.
Mr. Fred, here's the thing.
If you really want to help me,
let's sue the Rabbit Home Center?
Since you're a lawyer,
you can help me sue them, you know?
A tip, as a lawyer.
Revenge doesn't work.
Forget about it, Brenda.
It's bad for your health.
-Judges don't like that.
-Mr. Fred.
I don't want to be annoying,
but I have to say this.
-I'm not being rude. It's not revenge.
-Sure.
It's not. I know,
I've heard this advice before.
-Revenge gave my mom an ulcer.
-See?
It's about justice, Mr. Fred.
Justice has a new name now,
it's called revenge? No.
It's justice.
What they did to me was wrong.
-What they did was very wrong.
-Yes.
You need to see my termination papers.
They're awful!
And if justice fails, let me tell you,
then I'll go looking for revenge.
I'll go after the bastard
who did this to me.
-I'll get him. I'll find…
-For the love of God.
-I'll help you!
-You'll help me, Mr. Fred?
-Are you serious?
-I'll help you. Of course.
My God, Mr. Fred. I'm getting emotional.
-There's no need.
-You are a good man!
You are a great man. Thank you so much.
Look, I even brought my ID
so you can take care of this for me.
When can you help me?
WELCOME
Mr. Fred, you're still at home?
Beth, look,
people with kids are never on time.
In fact, people don't even expect
parents to be on time.
Jesus Christ,
where are my car keys? Again.
Malu, Clacla, get ready,
for the love of God, Daddy's late.
Is Dante there?
His whole family is here.
His wife, his kids.
So get ready, Mr. Fred,
for the love of God.
And hurry up.
RABBIT HOME CENTER
24TH FAMILY DAY
-I swear I'll give it back.
-Guys, I found my keys.
It was here the whole-- Huh?
Brenda? I thought you were off today.
Mr. Fred, I forgot my ID.
-It's okay, we'll find it.
-Okay, thanks.
I also lose a lot of stuff
running around here. Come here.
-Sometimes they're here.
-Excuse me.
-Sometimes they're in the drawer.
-Mm-hmm.
-What's this?
-What?
This is gorgeous, Mr. Fred.
-Is it your wife's?
-Yes, it is.
-Aunt Simone says she has great taste.
-Yes.
I love it.
She has great taste
and she's a lot of fun.
-You'll love her.
-I will, I'm sure.
Let me check these drawers too.
-Okay.
-All right?
I'm so excited to sue them, Mr. Fred.
The Rabbit Home Center people.
They're such bad people.
They don't appreciate us.
But this time, they will. You know why?
Compensation!
Found it! Brenda, I found your ID.
Where do you work?
What do you mean by "where"?
Because where…
Do you mean the neighborhood?
What?
-Do you work at the Rabbit Home Center?
-Calm down, okay? Breathe.
Let's be civil, it's all right.
Did you think it was fair to fire me
for three screws out of a box of 100?
Brenda, you stole.
I-- They-- They pressured me.
How were you going to be my lawyer?
Were you going to sue yourself?
I'm not even a lawyer.
Look, not everyone has
the same opportunities, okay?
Not everyone gets a second,
third, or fourth chance.
Not everyone has the privilege
of not being cut off after one mistake.
I think you're not considering
the fact that you committed a crime.
-You stole, Brenda.
-Three screws from a million-dollar store.
I was making minimum wage.
It's not about the number of screws,
Brenda, it's about character.
-Character?
-Character.
Look, Mr. Fred, I quit.
-Huh?
-I quit.
I'm leaving.
I won't give you the satisfaction
of firing me twice.
I'm out,
but this time it's because I want to.
How could he fire Brenda?
-I know.
-He's coming.
What?
I changed my mind.
So we are a family
We're going to Family Day
How nice, you guys.
This is going to be fun.
It's gonna be peace and love.
That's right, everyone.
It's our Family Day!
-And now it's time for our mascot…
-Hey, let's go, guys.
…to light the Rabbit Home Center's
Family Olympics
and warm our hearts.
-Let's go. Three, two, one.
-Rabbit, rabbit!
Rabbit, rabbit!
That's it, may the best one win!
There you go.
The Rabbit Home Center Games
are officially open!
Go, Fred!
-Red!
Hold on, wait a second.
-Go, Dad!
-Brazil's defense!
Hold the horns, man!
-Yellow!
He won't let go.
And the yellow team scores another point!
Red team just couldn't
make it happen this time.
The rivalry between the red team
and the yellow team is heating up.
-Pull!
-For the love of God, go!
-Go!
-No way!
-Go, Dad!
-Pull!
-Go!
No!
The yellow team scores!
-Yellow!
Look at that.
Perfect.
That's awesome.
Didn't you want us to come, Dad?
-It's our only chance to win.
-Yeah, and it's worth more points.
-Are you going, Beth?
-No.
Twenty points for the yellow team,
ten for the red team.
-Yellow!
-Suck it, red!
Hold him for me, please.
Guys, please, aim for the middle.
-One mistake can be fatal.
-Ready?
Yes, but don't ask me again,
because I might regret it, my love.
Dad, we need to tell you something.
Honey, I love you all very much too.
-It's not that.
-What is it?
It was good that Mom went on that trip.
We got to know each other better.
That's so beautiful,
Daddy loves you very much too, okay?
But we didn't like what we saw.
-What?
-And we think you should go on a trip too.
-Yeah.
-Right?
Guys, stop, get me out of here. Sir!
I want out. Where's Beth?
Tom Tom might need me.
-You don't even understand him.
-But if I did,
he'd probably be saying, "Dad,
get out of there, it's too dangerous."
He'd tell you to hold on tight, Dad.
-Just like a wing screw.
-Huh?
No.
No. You've become a bad person, son.
Look, say "bye" to Daddy, he's gonna roll.
No. Who are you?
What kind of kids are you? No!
I can't believe you're doing this!
I can't believe it! Jesus, help me!
Help!
The rabbit!
-Didn't we overdo it?
-Help!
Probably.
Oh my God. What are you doing, man?
-Just a second.
-Give me your hand. I'll help you.
-Are you insane? Hold my hand.
-Take me out of here.
Fred…
-Wait a second, I'll-- Hold this.
-Wait.
Wait, I can't see. Wait!
My God.
Help! My tail is on fire.
-Fred, do something.
-Calm down, Mr. Pontes. Calm down!
-Do something, fix this mess! What?
-Calm down!
Run, people. Run!
-Run!
-Somebody help me! It's real fire!
I don't wanna die!
Help, people, help!
Water!
RABBIT HOME CENTER
24TH FAMILY DAY
Yeah, Tom Tom.
-You can go.
-Can I go?
Excuse me…
You can go, Daddy.
-Can I? Can I go?
-Mm-hmm. You're free to go.
Bye, Tom Tom. Bye, son.
-He's fine, right?
-Yes. Go.
Yeah. That's right.
CHILDREN'S DOCUMENTS
This is what I need.
-Hi, Beth.
-Hi, Mr. Fred.
Listen, the board scheduled a meeting
for 5:00 p.m. today.
But how? I'm on leave.
They know you're on leave, Mr. Fred,
but they said it's urgent, okay?
Oh my God. Anything else, Beth?
If you have a rose quartz,
a Saint George medallion,
a lucky charm, bring it.
All right. Thank you, Beth.
You're welcome.
Okay. I know it's here.
Oh, honey.
So beautiful.
Damn.
Here it is.
Let's see.
What?
BIRTH CERTIFICATE: MALU GUIMARÃES
It says 9 p.m.
I knew it.
I mean, I didn't know that I knew…
but I knew.
I knew it, honey.
Damn.
My punctual girl, Daddy knew it, sweetie.
If this had been earlier,
he'd be at daycare.
Since you scheduled the meeting for later,
he's here, but it's all under control.
It's a rabbit, son. Thank you, by the way.
Well, gentlemen.
As you all know,
I'll be stepping away from the company,
and I'd like to announce
the new General Manager.
From now on, you'll officially report
to Dante.
As for you, Fred,
given the recent unfortunate events,
it's no longer appropriate
for you to remain Head of HR.
The Board has agreed
to move you
to the Institutional Relations Department.
-That's it.
-Daddy.
What did you say, son?
Fred, are you serious?
Did you say "Daddy"?
-Daddy.
-Daddy. He said "Daddy."
Have you lost--
Have you lost all respect? I'm speaking.
No, I haven't, Mr. Pontes.
I completely understand why
you'd want to keep me at the company.
I know I'm an excellent professional.
But at the moment,
it makes no sense for me to be here.
It doesn't. So, as the Head of HR,
I fire myself and, as an employee,
I accept my resignation.
I'll come by later and get
everything sorted out, severance and all.
But for now,
we're out of here.
We're leaving, right, Tom Tom?
We're going home to draw and be happy,
because I love you, sweetie.
Congratulations to all of you.
Let me grab my things.
Say "bye" to everyone.
Bye, everyone.
Bye.
We're very happy. Bye.
"Daddy." He said "Daddy."
He said "Daddy."
Oh, Mr. Fred, I'll miss you.
Really?
Really, Mr. Fred. I have a psychiatrist
who prescribes some strong medication.
Rose quartz is nice, you know?
But sometimes prescription meds
are what do the trick.
I'm fine. We're fine.
Bye, Beth. We're fine and happy,
all right?
Right? We're great, Beth.
We are great, aren't we?
We're wonderful.
It's here.
Mr. Fred, what are you doing here?
I look a mess.
Tom Tom!
Mr. Fred, this girl has worked
in so many places
I didn't even know
the last one was your company.
I'm sorry about Brenda.
I'm so embarrassed I wish I could hide.
Listen, I'm the one
who needs to apologize, okay?
-Is Brenda here?
-Yeah, she's upstairs.
-I'll go talk to her.
-Go on.
I'll stay here with Tom Tom.
Right, sweetie?
What are you doing here?
I came to give you a gift
and apologize, because…
-Did you buy that for me?
-No.
I mean, it is for you, but this one I…
-What?
-I stole it.
-No way.
-It's true.
And you're absolutely right,
that place is awful.
I was awful,
but that place has a way
of making us all more and more awful.
I'm sorry, okay?
And I can get you another job,
in a better place.
Thank you, then.
Once I get my life in order, because…
I quit too.
-You quit?
-Mm-hmm.
-No way.
-Yes.
-For real?
-For real.
Do you see that thing over there?
-Yes.
-It's half assembled.
There. It's a piece of furniture
I bought for Aunt Simone.
She wanted something for the living room.
So I gave it to her.
I bought it in 78 installments,
I didn't know I'd get fired.
I ordered it unassembled
because assembled was more expensive.
It arrived with three screws missing.
Where did I buy it?
-Rabbit Home Center.
-No.
-But we can fix that now.
-Let's do it.
There you go.
Thank you.
I heard about Family Day.
-I'm sorry, okay? I overdid it.
-No problem at all.
I mean, none of my organs are
where they're supposed to be anymore.
The farm's been devastated,
but everything's under control.
But I know I was being very selfish.
-Yeah.
-So Roberta has every right
to be upset with me.
Mm-hmm.
And my kids have every right
not to like me anymore.
No, stop it. Of course they like you.
Your kids are really cool.
They wouldn't be so cool
if you weren't too.
It's done. It looks good.
You're good.
Your kids like you.
But they're not even talking to me.
But it must be hard for them, right?
Knowing they hurt you
with that Family Day prank.
Talk to them, man. You're their father.
Am I still?
It has a translation, you know?
In Portuguese, it's Dia da Família.
How the tables have turned.
I'm a fast learner.
Give me a hug.
You're lucky I'm not a Scorpio.
-Thanks. And what are you?
-I don't hold grudges.
-I'm a Taurus.
-Like Tom Tom.
-Tom Tom is a Taurus?
-You didn't know?
-I didn't.
-Why do you think he eats so much?
-Maybe he has worms?
-No, he eats fruits, rice, beans…
Brand-new diaper, right? Yay!
-Score!
-Yeah!
-Rest.
-Yeah! That's it.
That's it, girl!
She's got nothing on the left!
Nothing on the left! Hit it left!
Okay? Focus, relax, breathe.
Hit her left side. Focus, okay?
-Are you listening?
-Yeah.
-Go, hit her left side.
-Okay, Dad.
Son, I can't believe
you were studying anatomy
with my best friend's daughter.
She's practically your cousin.
You're offended.
That's all you have to say?
I'm not offended, I'm a survivor.
I didn't put my kids in a giant ball.
I survived by some miracle.
-Score!
-Some miracle!
Us surviving with you
taking care of us was also a miracle, Dad.
Jesus, honey.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry too, Dad.
Okay.
Yeah, Dad. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Dad.
I'm sorry, guys.
It was my bad.
Maybe you could save
family therapy for another time.
Just a second.
Another time that never comes.
If he's anything like you,
it will never be the right time.
What the hell, Júlia?
Disrespecting your mother
just because you have an audience?
When we get home, we'll chat. Don't worry.
No. When we get home,
you'll be on your phone.
See what I mean?
It's so sad to see a family fighting.
They're fighting,
but at least they're talking.
You don't talk or fight.
You never even asked
if I like these games.
-What do you mean, son?
-Quiet down, everyone.
-You're disturbing the game!
-That's right.
You're the referee,
not a family court judge, okay?
Hey!
-The man asked for silence!
-Yes.
Anyone who's not interested
in the tennis match is free to leave.
-Me!
-What?
I'm exhausted from practicing every day
and getting up early to do it.
I don't even like tennis.
I do it because you bug me.
But, honey…
Also because I know it's important to you.
Oh, for crying out loud.
I didn't even want to come,
and we won't have a match?
Hey, lady, do you mind?
-Go fu--
-Hey! Calm down.
Look at the example we're setting here.
Really? You're talking
about setting an example?
-What do you mean by that, son?
-You don't pay attention to me…
We came to see my friend.
These annoying people
are bothering my daughter.
Wait, guys.
Just a second.
Relax, you're nervous.
That's normal, honey.
There's no need for that.
Guys, team, gather up.
It's the perfect time for us to leave.
-Let's go?
-Let's go.
Come on, son.
Come here, honey. Let's play.
You're amazing!
Playing… It's all right.
Let's go. We'll be happier
once we're out of this madness.
Look, my little crew, my loves,
I know you're upset,
with those grumpy faces,
but the universe just showed us
a spectacular example
of a dysfunctional family.
So, it could be much worse.
So, Dad may be doing poorly,
but it could be much worse.
Now… No. Now I want to see
everyone helping me clean up this mess.
-No.
-Guys!
-Tom Tom.
-Tom Tom is going to…
-Tom Tom!
Look who's here!
Huh?
-Mom? Weren't you coming tomorrow?
-My son!
-Mommy's back. Squeeze Mommy.
-I missed you, Mom!
I missed you.
You look beautiful, Mom.
-Look who's here.
-You're here!
-She's here.
She's here!
-Mommy's here.
-I missed you so much!
Oh, God. Jesus Christ.
Hey, team, he pooped.
-It's my turn to change him.
-No, let me!
Yeah?
-Yeah.
-I'm gonna watch them, okay, Mom?
And I'll also put your things away.
You must be tired from the trip.
-Kisses.
-Kisses. Bye.
-Wonderful.
-What did you do with my kids?
-Huh?
-Did you drug them?
-No!
-My children, Fred.
-How are you? I missed you so much.
-You look beautiful.
My God.
-Were you desperate?
-No.
-Felt like curling up and crying?
No? You didn't age
a hundred years in one day?
I aged a little. But it's okay,
you're back and you're beautiful.
I need to tell you
something very important.
-Me too.
-Are you serious? For the love of God.
You're back
with something important to tell me.
You go first.
Honey, I don't want to be
a full-time mom and housewife.
I need to be happy. I need to…
For the sake of our family,
I'm going back to work.
Are you serious?
And I quit my job, honey.
-No way.
-I quit my job.
-Really?
-Really.
-But now what?
-Now you'll be the breadwinner.
I'll take care of things.
It will be wonderful, we're a team.
And you're back, and beautiful.
-I love you.
-I love you. I missed you so much.
Oh my God.
Ew!
-Oh, hi!
-Mom, we found out Dad's terrible.
But at least he tries.
And we missed you so much.
But we're happy you look beautiful.
-What's it like there?
-Salvador is so beautiful.
It's so nice. I've already decided.
At least once a year,
I'll spend ten days there.
Wait. Gather up, guys, team meeting.
Let's decide if we'll let Mom
keep going to Salvador.
What's this attachment to Salvador?
Guys, it's magical.
-There's an energy, a glow.
-Turn that glow down a bit.
No, keep your beautiful glow,
but here with us. We need you.
I know all the dance routines, okay?
Mom's the new redhead from É o Tchan now.
-What is É o Tchan, Mom?
-No way, João!
-I'll play it now.
-It's an axé band.
-Come on, shake it.
-No. I learned how to change diapers.
-Yeah.
-To get kids settled into daycare.
Now I have to learn É o Tchan dance moves?
Loosen up. You can do it.
-Just a second, Beta.
-Come on!
-Yes, Malu!
-Come here, Clacla.
Help your sister. We have to go under it.
-I can't do that.
-Higher, for the love of God.
My back. Come on!
Jesus Christ!
This is such a good song!
-Here! Hey!
-Yeah.
-Jump!
-Come on, move it.
DADDY'S IN TROUBLE
Fred, you're not going to believe this.
Did Beth tell you?
Dante's wife heard
about Roberta's arrangement
and took off for Miami,
leaving the kids with him.
Don't even know when she's coming back.
Matheus, what a juicy piece of gossip!
The best I get is school gossip here.
I need some grown-up gossip.
So you're saying Dante is…
The guy's emasculated.
He shows up for work with the same outfit
every day, like a cartoon character.
Everyone's saying Pontes was
the one holding everything together.
Oh! Wasn't he "the best in Cambridge"?
With his perfect family?
Even Tom Tom is laughing.
Aren't you, buddy?
He asked for your number.
Wanted to know if you were still idle.
Idle? What do you mean, Matheus?
I was idle at Rabbit Home Center.
Here at home, I'm doing lambaerobics,
fit dance, CrossFit,
but not lifting gym weights.
I'm lifting kids' backpacks.
Hey, he just sent me a message!
Hold on, let me listen!
Yo, Fred! Long time no see.
How are you, my friend? It's Dante.
You know we'll welcome you back
whenever you want.
Rabbit Home Center's your family.
I guarantee a great salary.
Name your price, all right?
Are you interested? Oh!
Call me back. I'm waiting.
Don't forget about me, Fred.
HONEY! BETINHA! LISTEN TO THIS!
Is that Dante? Jesus!
YEAH!!!!
Wait until he finds out
that the lawyer helping Brenda
sue Rabbit Home Center is me.
He's going to freak out!
Honey, can you send me some pictures
of the kids? I miss them.
Okay, I'll send them.
But as soon as you see the mess
they're making around the house,
you'll stop missing them.
Mr. Fred, I love working
at Mrs. Roberta's office.
Who knew? The worst thing
to ever happen to me, you,
led to the best thing
to ever happen to me, Mrs. Roberta.
This woman is not a lawyer, Mr. Fred.
She's a dragon tamer.
You should see what she does around here.
She'll destroy that bastard Dante.
She'll make him cry screw tears.
You'll see.
What the hell is this?
-Did you like it? The kids made it.
-I thought so. I could tell right away.
I would never expect
such creativity from you.
With all due respect, Mr. Fred.
MATHEUS
I JUST HEARD! DANTE IS DES…
Matheus, he's desperate.
Should I let him know I'm not coming back,
or let him suffer for a while?
Dad, Clarice's hitting me.
Clacla, stop! João, you're the oldest.
Set an example. God! Where are you going?
-Who's outside?
-No one, Dad. A friend.
Look, when your mom gets here,
we're going to have a talk.
It's Double Tuesday.
She's going to the bar with Brenda.
Did you hear that, Matheus? Hold on.
Roberta, I'll need ten days in Salvador.
Okay? In the summer!
-I want to go too.
-Figure it out, Betinha!
Timbalada!
Subtitle translation by: J. Jones